Papers of Morris K. Udall, 1920-1995
University of Arizona Library Special Collections
- Legislative Files, 1961-1990
  - Legislative Correspondence, 1961-1990
    - 88th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Manpower Utilization Subcommittee. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - 88th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-O'Harre-Udall Proposal for Recruitment, Training. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - 88th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Hearing Files, HR 319 and Related Bills. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - 88th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Manpower Symposium. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - 88th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Morris K. Udall, Chairman, HR 7401. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - 88th Congress: Public Works-General. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - 88th Congress: Public Works-Interstate Highway Business. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - 88th Congress: Rules-John Young Appointment. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - 88th Congress: Un-American Activities. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - 88th Congress: Veterans-General. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - 88th Congress: Veterans-World War I Pensions. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - 88th Congress: Veterans-VA Legislative Calendar. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - 88th Congress: Joint Committees, Commissions and Boards-General. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-Miscellaneous. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-Excise Taxes. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-Beef. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-Taxes. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 21-24)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-Medical Care. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-Social Security. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 26)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-Tax Reform Fact Sheet. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 27)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-Medical Care. 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 28)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-Income Tax Information. 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-Medicare. 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 2-9)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-Trade Expansion Act, HR 9900. 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-GATT Tariff. 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - 88th Congress: Ways and Means-Reciprocal Trade. 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - 88th Congress: Special, Select and Joint Committees-District of Columbia. 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - 88th Congress: Special, Select and Joint Committees-Science and Astronautics. 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - 88th Congress: Miscellaneous Legislation-General. 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 15-17)
    - 88th Congress: Miscellaneous Legislation-Resolutions Received. 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - 88th Congress: Miscellaneous Legislation-Questionnaire. 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - 88th Congress: Miscellaneous Legislation-Kennedy Death. 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - 89th Congress: Agriculture-Miscellaneous. 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - 89th Congress: Agriculture-Background, Secretary of Agriculture Freeman. 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - 89th Congress: Agriculture-Cotton. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - 89th Congress: Agriculture-Bread Tax. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - 89th Congress: Appropriations-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - 89th Congress: Appropriations-School Lunch Program. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - 89th Congress: Armed Services-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - 89th Congress: Armed Services-Milk Contracts. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - 89th Congress: Armed Services-National Guard Technician. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - 89th Congress: Banking and Currency-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - 89th Congress: Banking and Currency-Tight Money. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - 89th Congress: Banking and Currency-Demonstration Cities. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - 89th Congress: Education and Labor-Education. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - 89th Congress: Education and Labor-Right to Work, Repeal of Taft Hartley 14.B. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 14-19)
    - 89th Congress: Education and Labor-Minimum Wage. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - 89th Congress: Education and Labor-Labor Subcommittee, General. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - 89th Congress: Education and Labor-Mine Safety, HR 5596. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - 89th Congress: Education and Labor-School Aid. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 23)
    - 89th Congress: Education and Labor-Poverty Fight. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 24)
    - 89th Congress: Education and Labor-Tax Deduction for Teachers. 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 25)
    - 89th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - 89th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Connally Reservation (World Court). 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - 89th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Foreign Aid. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - 89th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Vietnam Hearings. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 4-5)
    - 89th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Vietnam. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 6-8)
    - 89th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Vietnam Peace Effort. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - 89th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Vietnam Telegram from the University of Arizona Faculty and Replies. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - 89th Congress: Government Operations-General. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - 89th Congress: Government Operations-Auto Safety. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - 89th Congress: Government Operations-Urban Development. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - 89th Congress: Government Operations-Population. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 14-15)
    - 89th Congress: House Administration-General. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - 89th Congress: House Administration- HR 17618, Election Reform. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - 89th Congress: Interior and Insular Affairs-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 18-20)
    - 89th Congress: Interior and Insular Affairs-Irrigation and Reclamation. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - 89th Congress: Interior and Insular Affairs-Indian Affairs. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - 89th Congress: Interior and Insular Affairs-Irrigation Subcommittee, Basic Information. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - 89th Congress: Interior and Insular Affairs-National Parks. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - 89th Congress: Interior and Insular Affairs-Public Lands. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - 89th Congress: Interior and Insular Affairs-Indiana Dunes, HR 3833. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - 89th Congress: Interior and Insular Affairs-Indian Land Leases, HR 7648. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - 89th Congress: Interior and Insular Affairs-Sonoran Desert National Park, HR11695. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - 89th Congress: Interior and Insular Affairs-Redwood National Park, HR 11998. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 29)
    - 89th Congress: Interior and Insular Affairs-Eddie Earl-Avra Valley Land, HR 8156. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 30)
    - 89th Congress: Interior and Insular Affairs-Grand Canyon Dams. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 31)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 32)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-CATV Cable. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 33)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Community TV, HR 7715. 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 34)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Airline Strike. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Broadcasting. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Quality Stabilization. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Railway Labor Act. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Colorado River, HR 9752. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Humane Treatment of Dogs. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Humane Treatment of Animals. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Hart Bill-Optometrists. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Labeling, HR 15958. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - 89th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Federal Drug Administration, Food Labeling. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - 89th Congress: Judiciary-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - 89th Congress: Judiciary-Prayer. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - 89th Congress: Judiciary-Immigration. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - 89th Congress: Judiciary-Reapportionment, HR 14765. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - 89th Congress: Judiciary-Civil Rights Bill, HR 14765. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 15-16)
    - 89th Congress: Judiciary-Voting Rights. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - 89th Congress: Judiciary-Truth in Packaging. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - 89th Congress: Judiciary-Presidential Succession. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - 89th Congress: Judiciary-Morris K. Udall Bill, HJR 211. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - 89th Congress: Judiciary-Morris K. Udall Bill, HJR 405. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - 89th Congress: Merchant Marines and Fisheries-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 23-24)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Pay Bill Plaudits. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Pay Bill. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Compensation Subcommittee. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 27)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Retirement Subcommittee. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 28)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Zip Codes. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 29)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Cost of Living, HR 7401. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 30)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Cost of Living Allowance Bill, HR 8390. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 31)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Committee Rules. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 32)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Manpower Utilization. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 33)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Size and Weight of Parcel Post Shipments, HR 12367. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 34)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Reverse Discrimination (Potomac Institute & Dallas PO). 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 35)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Redistricting, HR 2857. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 36)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Annuities, HR 3015 / HR 3026. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 37)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Mail Fraud, HR 6102. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 38)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Overseas Teachers Pay, HR 6845. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 39)
    - 89th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Pay Bill, HR 14123. 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 40)
    - 89th Congress: Public Works-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - 89th Congress: Public Works-Federal Water Pollution Control Act Amendment, S 2947. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - 89th Congress: Rules-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - 89th Congress: Rules-Committee on Rules, HCR 55 / HCR 80. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - 89th Congress: Rules-Un-American Activities Committee. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - 89th Congress: Veterans Affairs-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - 89th Congress: Ways and Means-Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - 89th Congress: Ways and Means-Duty. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - 89th Congress: Ways and Means-Medicare. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - 89th Congress: Ways and Means-Social Security. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - 89th Congress: Ways and Means-Dodd Bill, S 1592. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - 89th Congress: Ways and Means-Anti-gun Bill Tape. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - 89th Congress: Ways and Means-Medical Care. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - 89th Congress: Ways and Means-Excise Tax. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 14-15)
    - 89th Congress: Ways and Means-Taxation. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - 89th Congress: Ways and Means-Guns. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - 89th Congress: Ways and Means-Imports. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - 89th Congress: Ways and Means-Employment Legislation. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - 89th Congress: Special, Select and Joint Committees-District of Columbia, Home Rule 1965. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - 89th Congress: Special, Select and Joint Committees-District of Columbia, School Appropriations. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - 89th Congress: Special, Select and Joint Committees-District of Columbia, Miscellaneous. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - 89th Congress: Special, Select and Joint Committees-Science and Astronautics. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - 89th Congress: Special, Select and Joint Committees-Small Business Committee. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - 89th Congress: Special, Select and Joint Committees-Atomic Energy. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - 89th Congress: Special, Select and Joint Committees-Economic. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - 89th Congress: Special, Select and Joint Committees-Printing. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - 89th Congress: Special, Select and Joint Committees-Reorganization of Congress and Congressional Reform. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - 89th Congress: Special, Select and Joint Committees-Navajo-Hopi Administration. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - 89th Congress: Miscellaneous Legislative. 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 30)
    - 90th Congress: Agriculture-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - 90th Congress: Agriculture-Cotton. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - 90th Congress: Agriculture-Dairy and Poultry. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - 90th Congress: Agriculture-Conservation and Credit. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - 90th Congress: Agriculture-Cotton Imports, HR 10915. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - 90th Congress: Appropriations-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - 90th Congress: Appropriations-Agriculture and Related Agencies. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - 90th Congress: Appropriations-Defense. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - 90th Congress: Appropriations-Interior and Related Agencies. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - 90th Congress: Appropriations-Labor, HEW and Related Agencies. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - 90th Congress: Appropriations-Military Construction. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - 90th Congress: Appropriations-Poverty Program. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - 90th Congress: Appropriations-Public Works. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - 90th Congress: Appropriations-Transportation Subcommittee. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - 90th Congress: Appropriations-Highway Funds. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - 90th Congress: Appropriations-Treasury, Post Office and Executive Office. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - 90th Congress: Armed Services-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 17-18)
    - 90th Congress: Banking and Currency-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 19-20)
    - 90th Congress: Banking and Currency-Housing. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - 90th Congress: Banking and Currency-Bank Supervision and Insurance. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - 90th Congress: Banking and Currency-Small Business. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 23)
    - 90th Congress: Education and Labor-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - 90th Congress: Education and Labor-Education. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - 90th Congress: Education and Labor-Labor. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - 90th Congress: Education and Labor-Poverty. 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 1-2)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Vietnam. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 3-11)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Vietnam,Replies from Peace Letters. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Vietnam Speech. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Vietnam Hearings Report. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Far East and Asia. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Africa. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Consular Convention. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Europe. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Foreign Aid. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Foreign Economic Policy. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Inter-American Affairs. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Near East. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - 90th Congress: Foreign Affairs-Biafra. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - 90th Congress: Government Operations-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - 90th Congress: House Administration-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - 90th Congress: House Administration-Election Reform, HR 1412. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 26)
    - 90th Congress: House Administration-Powell Letters/Out-of State. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 27-29)
    - 90th Congress: House Administration-Powell Letters/Answered. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 30)
    - 90th Congress: House Administration-Powell, Adam Clayton. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 31)
    - 90th Congress: House Administration-Powell Letter from District. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 32)
    - 90th Congress: House Administration-Powell Seating. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 33)
    - 90th Congress: House Administration-Powell. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 34)
    - 90th Congress: House Administration-Powell, 1966. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 35)
    - 90th Congress: House Administration-Powell, Act III. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 36)
    - 90th Congress: House Administration-Powell, January 1969. 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 37)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 1-3)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-Indian Affairs. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-Irrigation and Reclamation. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-Mines and Mining. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-National Parks. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 7-9)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-National Parks, Chiricahua National Monument. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-Public Lands. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-Public Lands, Colorado Land Dispute. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-Territorial and Insular Affairs. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-Sonoran Desert, HR 1409. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-San Raphael Conference. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-Scenic Rivers. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-Redwoods National Park. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 17-18)
    - 90th Congress: Interior-North Cascades, Field Inspection. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - 90th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 20-22)
    - 90th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Transportation and Aeronautics. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - 90th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Health and Welfare. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - 90th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Communication and Power. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - 90th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Aviation User Charges. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 26)
    - 90th Congress: Interstate and Foreign Commerce-Weight Limits on Highways, S 2658. 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 27)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 1-4)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Anti-Riot Bill. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Civil Rights. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 6-8)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Open Housing. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Claims. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Constitutional Amendment. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Copyright Law. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Green Card Investigation. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 13-17)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Immigration. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Liberty Amendment. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 19-21)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Poor People's March. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 22)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Prayer Amendment. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 23)
    - 90th Congress: Judiciary-Revision of Laws. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 24)
    - 90th Congress: Merchant Marines and Fisheries-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 25)
    - 90th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 26-28)
    - 90th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Compensation. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 29-30)
    - 90th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Census and Statistics. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 31)
    - 90th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Civil Service. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 32)
    - 90th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Mail Fraud., HR 1411. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 33)
    - 90th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Manpower. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 34)
    - 90th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Personnel Cutbacks. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 35)
    - 90th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Postal Operations. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 36)
    - 90th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Postal Rates. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 37-38)
    - 90th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Retirement, Insurance and Health Benefits. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 39)
    - 90th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Dulski Testimonial Dinner Fracas (clippings). 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 40)
    - 90th Congress: Post Office and Civil Service-Wage Board Bill. 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 41)
    - 90th Congress: Public Works-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - 90th Congress: Public Works-Air Pollution. 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - 90th Congress: Public Works-Flood Control. 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - 90th Congress: Public Works-Roads. 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - 90th Congress: Public Works-Watershed Development. 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - 90th Congress: Rules-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - 90th Congress: Un-American Activities-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - 90th Congress: Un-American Activities-HR 148. 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - 90th Congress: Veterans-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 9-10)
    - 90th Congress: Veterans-Compensation and Pension. 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - 90th Congress: Ways and Means-Miscellaneous. 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 12-13)
    - 90th Congress: Ways and Means-Excise Taxation. 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 14)